Hi Kevin, good to have you in South
Florida. What would you describe as your
best skill as a slot receiver? Is it
speed, shiftiness, elusiveness, ability
to accelerate after catching? And also
slot receivers in the NFL that you
enjoyed watching growing up in recent
years, guys. Maybe you patterned some
things of your game after.
>> I say two things. Um, I say getting
open, but I also say catching the ball.
Uh you'll really see me catch the ball.
No matter if it's contested, over the
shoulder, um anything. I just it's
catching the ball. Uh guys, um I kind of
watch and model my game after growing
up. Um I say Amar St. Brown, guys like
Antonio Brown with route running, Amarra
with strong hands and just being strong
and just being um
very um helpful on third downs.
Thanks so much,
>> Chris.
>> Hey, Kevin. Chris Perkins from the South
Florida Sun Sentinel. How you doing?
>> I'm doing great. How you doing?
>> I'm good. I'm good. Uh, I'm doing a a
combo story on the lower picks, the
lower round draft picks on your draft
night experience or draft day experience
and whether you consider yourself an
underdog. Tell me about your draft day
experience. Some guys are grateful to
have their names called. Some guys are
upset because they thought they lasted
too long. What was your draft day
experience like?
>> Um, I had a party day two. I expected to
go off day two, but I didn't. But I was
still blessed and happy. Went to sleep,
woke up with the same mindset I had day
two. Um, I'm just happy to get the
opportunity to play. Um, I still got the
opportunity to step on the field,
fulfill my dreams, and take things day
by day. But, you know, of course, it
added some fuel. It added it definitely
added some fuel. more motivation, but
I'm like I said, I'm just blessed with
the opportunity to play.
>> And do you consider yourself an an
underdog going into the league? I mean,
you played at Missouri, a SEC school,
um, but you were a a a lower round pick.
How what is your mindset, your mentality
coming into the league?
>> I feel like just being a part of that
1%, you always be the underdog. It's
it's hard to get to um where I am and
just where we are as players. But my
mindset coming to lead, of course, I'm
going have that underdog mindset. I got
to go prove myself. I got to go make the
team uh earn guys trust, earn coaches
trust. So, of course, I got that
underdog mindset. I just got that proven
mindset.
>> Congrats, man.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> David.
>> Hey, Kevin. David Peronis from the South
Florida Sun Sentinel. Welcome to South
Florida and congrats on being drafted.
>> Yes, sir. I appreciate it.
>> Yeah, this franchise, a lot of turnover
at wide receiver this offseason.
Obviously, they don't have Tyreek Hill
and Jaylen Waddle, the combination they
had for so many years. Now, you're part
of uh three receivers in this draft
class. A lot of guys getting a chance.
What do you think of the opportunity uh
with this team that you just got drafted
to?
>> Like you said, uh the guys they had in
the past, they're gone. So, with this
new staff and everything comes
opportunity. So it's just time to come
there, take things day by day and
compete. Like you said, everyone got to
earn the new coaches trust. They got to
earn just earn things. So I love the
opportunity that's in front of me. And
looking at your college years, I saw
four schools in four years. Can you
explain why that was and maybe one thing
you learned at every spot uh with
Jackson State, Louisville, Mississippi
State, and Missouri? I'm going to put
you on the spot. One thing you learned
at each one of those stops. I enjoy my
times at every school and learn
different things. As I was younger, I
was just getting more mature, more
consistent, learning about more things I
can do just to help myself and help my
team. Um, when I left Jackson State, um,
had a great experience there, had great
teammates. Of course, my coach left, so
I decided to leave as well. Uh, Coach
Prime was a big reason why I went there.
When I left left there and went to
Louisville,
uh, my first scholarship came from the
University of Missouri out of high
school. I had a receiver coach. um
Garrick McGee, he was at um Louisville,
so I end up deciding to go there close
to home. Great conference and it was
just um a good mood at the time. Uh one
thing I learned, just keep fighting no
matter what. Uh went to Louisville as a
as an underdog team and went to the ACC
championship with the first year head
coaching first year team and we just
fought every single game no matter what.
Um when I left Louisville, that new rule
came out that I could transfer. didn't
know I was going to transfer to after
the um bowl game. Talked back with some
coaches and family. Ended up deciding to
go to Mississippi State. I went to
Mississippi State, loved everything that
came with it. Um Coach Levby, a guy that
believed in me. I appreciate him and
thank him to this day for everything he
has done. When I end up leaving there,
had great experience there as well. When
I left there is because of course NIL
back home, but I also had a daughter and
wanted to be close back to home to get
family help.
>> Excellent, man. Really appreciate that.
Thanks.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Omar,
>> so that was primarily my my question in
terms of the four schools cuz that's
what really stands out about your
resume. Um, one, why didn't you go to
Prime with Prime to Colorado? And two,
Louisville, you you said you went there
to to play for a coach that that
recruited you. Why? Like why the moving
the or instead of just staying at one
spot? And didn't you have to learn four
different offenses? Yeah, the four
different for offices was no problem.
Um, I'm good at learning things and
going out there and just executing it.
Um, leaving Louisville was just a family
decision. Uh, that's what I said. That
new rule had came out, decided things
would be better. Talked to some coaches
on the staff and feel like things would
be better if I moved on. Um, with coach
Prime, I end up deciding not to leave.
My family's from Denver, Colorado. I
decided not to even go there because I
just felt like me and my me and my
family just wanted more and wanted
something else. wanted to go to just a a
different team, different vibe.
>> Gotcha.
And and you've exclusively played in the
slot, it seems. Um have
>> and and return. I heard you like 16
touchdowns in high school on
>> Oh, yeah. I was crazy back in high
school. Return.
>> So, obviously, do you still feel like
you have that crazy ability?
>> Oh, yeah. Definitely. I display it.
>> Gotcha. Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
Isaiah
>> going on Kevin. Isaiah Smalls from the
Miami Herald. How are you?
>> I'm great. How you doing?
>> I'm good. I'm good. Congratulations
again. Um my question kind of follows
that same line, but I wanted to ask what
does the four schools in four years kind
of say about your ability to adapt and
how will that help you at the next
level?
>> When you go to four different schools,
you got to earn guys trust. Uh some you
might you got to earn guys respect. Some
guys when you first come in might not
respect you like you said they will look
at their resume and they assume things
but when you come in there less worries
and just all action and just show guys
what you're about and they respect you.
Earn guys trust you earn your coach's
trust. Um got to learn the playbook as
well. Had to go in learn four different
playbooks and I went to all the
different schools in the spring and
started at all of them in the spring. So
that shows you right away I come in
right away knowing the playbook, knowing
the coach's lingo and earning the
coaches trust.
>> Cool. Appreciate you. Congrats, man.
Welcome to Thank you,
>> Joe.
>> Hey, Kevin. It's uh Joe Shad in Palm
Beach. It's nice to to meet you. You
mentioned Antonio Brown earlier. Um
obviously had a tremendous career
despite being a sixthround pick. I still
don't know how he fell to the sixth
round, but um what parts of his on the-
field game do you try to uh encapsulate
for yourself?
>> Yeah, he's quick twitch. He's twitchy.
He's he get open. his route running, his
sales thing, his double moves, just
everything. His just all all around
game. Um when he was younger, his return
game, he was special. Um his yak, I just
feel like he's one he's one of the best
guys to do it. So I just try to take
little things and implicate it with my
my game.
>> I think you'll be on the roster if you
show that you can be a dangerous punt
returner. That that'll be like a cinch
for you. And I see you had a 67 yard uh
punt return last year. How do you
approach the punt return?
>> First thing you got to do is catch the
ball. Secure the ball. That's
everything. Eyes on the ball, catch the
ball, good feet, everything else. You
got to just practice hard. Practice
habits is everything. You practice hard,
take that serious like you said, that's
going to be my way. And I also think the
same thing. So, got to take those things
serious. Really watch film on things. uh
and just be an open book and learn
things.
>> Good stuff. Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Travis,
>> hey, what's up, Kevin? Congrats again uh
to being drafted by the Miami Dolphins
here. You've been talking a lot about
catching the football. I read that you
catch 300 balls a day on the Jugs
machine. I was curious how that started
for you,
>> man. As my dad a young age, I'm going to
say five, but I think it's before 5
years old. My dad had me catching tennis
balls a thousand times. Uh he had thrown
them off the wall. I wouldn't be looking
behind me and I catch the ball. He throw
them to me. I've been catching tennis
balls and football since I was younger.
My dad always throw it to me. So, that's
one thing my dad always wanted me to
have. Even though I played running back
growing up, catching the ball was
everything.
>> Is there any other crazy like
extracurricular work habit we should
know about that helped you get to this
point, you think?
>> Man, uh, the speed letter. I got good
feet, quick feet. I got the same speed
letter since I was 5 years old. I had
the same speed letter. So, I've been
doing the same things I'm doing now
since I was 5 years old with the speed
ladder.